{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_C._Clarke",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Hard_science_fiction",
    "human_readable": "Arthur C. Clarke's genre is Hard science fiction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9013341665267944,
            "question": "Describe the style of science fiction that Arthur C. Clarke is famous for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8808606863021851,
            "question": "What genre of fiction is Arthur C. Clarke known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219034671783447,
            "question": "What type of science fiction does Arthur C. Clarke write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7190588116645813,
            "question": "What kind of scientific accuracy is characteristic of Arthur C. Clarke's stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082950830459595,
            "question": "How does Arthur C. Clarke's writing approach science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5825663805007935,
            "question": "What distinguishes Hard science fiction from other subgenres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5341677069664001,
            "question": "Which literary category is associated with Arthur C. Clarke's works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47954773902893066,
            "question": "Give an example of a common theme in Hard science fiction."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44926509261131287,
            "question": "What are some key characteristics of Arthur C. Clarke's writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3310411274433136,
            "question": "Why is it important for Hard science fiction to be grounded in scientific principles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur C. Clarke's genre is Hard science fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8026_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key characteristics of Arthur C. Clarke's writing style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8026_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a common theme in Hard science fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8026_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which literary category is associated with Arthur C. Clarke's works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8026_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8026_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Arthur C. Clarke, including his writing style and the types of stories he wrote. The text also describes hard science fiction as a genre that prioritizes scientific accuracy and realism, and mentions Clarke's work in this context. Therefore, it can be concluded that the statement \"Arthur C. Clarke's genre is Hard science fiction\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Arthur C. Clarke's genre is Hard science fiction.\" The context mentions his work in hard science fiction, such as \"Through his distinguished career in science fiction, Sir Arthur C. Clarke (1917-2008) was known both for writing the hardest of hard science fiction stories and novels,\" and discusses other characteristics typical of hard science fiction like its focus on realism and scientific accuracy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}